<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Healthy lifestyle on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/healthy-lifestyle/</link><description>Recent content in Healthy lifestyle on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 01:34:45 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/healthy-lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>“Running helps to deal with problems”: the head of Lululemon is about sports</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63775e059a7947a05edaf4fd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 01:34:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63775e059a7947a05edaf4fd/</guid><description>Canadian company Lululemon Athletica, founded in 1998, has grown from a small firm specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s yoga pants to a sports retailer with 574 stores worldwide and a capitalization of $45.2 billion in just over 20 years. In 2020, the company ranked 25th in BrandZ&amp;rsquo;s Most Valuable Retail Brands. And in many respects this happened thanks to its current CEO Calvin McDonald.
He joined the company in 2018 and took over as CEO in 2021.</description></item><item><title>Melatonin: Should You Take It at Night?</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62d680439a79476eb2afeac9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 02:10:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62d680439a79476eb2afeac9/</guid><description>Melatonin is the most common sleep drug that can be found in pharmacies around the world and as a dietary supplement: it is available in tablets, dragées, capsules, drops, and even in the form of gummy bears. It is a natural remedy in the sense that melatonin from medical preparations is no different from the one produced by the body itself. And it really triggers sleep. But does it follow that a melatonin pill will help you get rid of insomnia?</description></item><item><title>How to instill in a child a love of sports and how this will help him in life</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636223429a7947a88809bb39/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 14:49:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636223429a7947a88809bb39/</guid><description>Physical activity is just as necessary for people as good nutrition and sleep. From birth, human development is associated with movement. It helps to improve sensory perception, to know your body, to learn the skills of large and fine motor skills, to form immunity. Thanks to physical activity, the child actively learns the world around him, develops intellectually and psychologically.
The importance of physical development began to speak in the era of humanism (XIV-XVI century).</description></item><item><title>Will genetic tests help you choose a diet and sport</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63578cac9a7947a5bbc41bee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:48:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63578cac9a7947a5bbc41bee/</guid><description>The first thing a person who decides to undergo genetic testing faces is the variety of offers from different companies. They can be divided into two large groups: diagnostic and screening.
1. Diagnostic tests are prescribed by a doctor when it is necessary to establish an accurate diagnosis. Usually, such a study is required if the external manifestations of the disease do not fit into the textbook clinical picture of a particular hereditary syndrome.</description></item><item><title>Six healthy habits of tennis player Anastasia Pivovarova</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635fa4b69a79476ff47251db/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 15:55:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635fa4b69a79476ff47251db/</guid><description>The endless scrolling of the news feed and the widespread instability increase the level of anxiety. But over the years of my sports career, I realized one thing: if you can’t avoid stress, and you can’t change your perception, you need to transform your routine. I will tell you about what helps me maintain mental health.
Daily Meditations According to a study by scientists from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, people who practice meditation are more resistant to stress than others.</description></item><item><title>Jira and Trello creator: "Successful people often feel like cheaters"</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e39369a7947074ed504a4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 01:38:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e39369a7947074ed504a4/</guid><description>About time management Mike Cannon-Brookes founded software company Atlassian with fellow student Scott Farquhar in 2002, right after graduating from university. Over 20 years, Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s capitalization has grown to $36 billion, and Cannon-Brooks&amp;rsquo; fortune to $9.4 billion. But despite the huge workload and responsibility, the entrepreneur always finds time for personal affairs.
He adheres to a strict daily routine and takes scheduling very seriously because &amp;ldquo;time cannot be turned back.&amp;rdquo; “I always try to find work-life balance,” he says.</description></item><item><title>“It’s all about concentration”: Robert Downey Jr. on Wing Chun</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636a3c039a794747e4e95bcf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:27:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636a3c039a794747e4e95bcf/</guid><description>During his career, 57-year-old American actor Robert Downey Jr. has starred in more than 70 films. He has won two Golden Globe Awards in 2001 and 2010. He also received several Oscar nominations. Downey Jr. has been on the Forbes list of Hollywood&amp;rsquo;s highest-paid actors four times, while topping the list three times.
But in the life of Downey Jr. there was a black streak. In 1992, at the age of 27, Downey played Charlie Chaplin in the film Chaplin and was named one of the most talented actors of the 1990s.</description></item><item><title>Five habits that will help you live longer</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635942059a79473ddeadb282/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 11:13:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635942059a79473ddeadb282/</guid><description>Eternal life is a question that has worried the best minds of mankind throughout history. What people have not tried to prolong their existence for at least a few years: from bathing in the blood of a deer to freezing in cryogenic chambers. Dystopias about immortal existence beat all records of popularity, and the younger generation is fond of vampires and elves, who are also endowed with this gift, according to the fiction of the writers.</description></item><item><title>Eight effective ways to add physical activity to your life</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634fb0ae9a794778c18fbec2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 11:28:06 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634fb0ae9a794778c18fbec2/</guid><description>Only one in five Russians walks 10,000 steps a day, an approximate amount needed to maintain heart tone and well-being. This result was shown by a survey of CDEK and the Guldog service. At the same time, almost a third of respondents walk less than 5 thousand steps a day, of which 11% do not even fulfill the minimum bar of 3 thousand steps.
Our study confirms these findings: more than a third of the participants admitted that they lead a passive lifestyle.</description></item><item><title>Tea and Paper Newspaper: How Google CEO Sundar Pichai Starts the Day</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636234309a7947ae4b67e1b7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 02:38:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636234309a7947ae4b67e1b7/</guid><description>An Indian-born metallurgical engineer and cricket enthusiast, Sundar Pichai has led Google since 2015. In December 2019, he was appointed head of parent company Alphabet, which under his leadership became the fourth major technology corporation with a market value of more than $1 trillion.
The position requires Pichai to be able to multitask. Nevertheless, despite the high load, it works calmly, measuredly and without fuss. In this he is helped by morning rituals, with which he begins every day.</description></item><item><title>Sober billionaires: Buffett, Rybakov, Durov - about giving up alcohol</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635a6cbd9a7947127de2ddcc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 14:34:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635a6cbd9a7947127de2ddcc/</guid><description>Igor Rybakov “When I came to university, alcohol was disgusting to me. More precisely, I was neutral to him. But what happened among the students at the university? Well, there, let&amp;rsquo;s try beer there, and so on &amp;hellip; And then what happened? Well, I began to apply a little beer, then more, more, ” recalled the co-founder of TechnoNIKOL. Now Rybakov is convinced that alcohol, like drugs, is a way to distract from difficulties and drown out stress, which only delays the solution of problems and thereby exacerbates them.</description></item></channel></rss>