<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Your daily dose reliable resources on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Your daily dose reliable resources on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 01:59:02 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Becoming Your Own Friend: How the Skill of Self-Compassion Can Save You From Burnout</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637718cd9a79478358512195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 01:59:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637718cd9a79478358512195/</guid><description>“You procrastinate again, and the deadlines are burning - pull yourself together!”. &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s a mistake upon a mistake, and you call yourself a professional?&amp;rdquo; “At this rate, this position can’t be sustained, watch how the rest give their best.” We are accustomed to strictly &amp;ldquo;motivate&amp;rdquo; ourselves to be productive, afraid that otherwise we will lose control over our lives, and with it - the chances for a successful career, harmonious relationships or sports achievements.</description></item><item><title>Why did the US start having problems with payments on car loans</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63777c999a7947ad48fb2802/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 01:54:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63777c999a7947ad48fb2802/</guid><description>The increase in the key rate in the US has now hit car owners who bought cars on credit. Interest rates on loans have risen, and inflation has significantly reduced the purchasing power of consumers. As a result, payment discipline among borrowers has shaken in the United States.
But the problem lies not only in unscrupulous car owners. Car prices also began to decline, and this led to a new round of problems.</description></item><item><title>Melatonin: Should You Take It at Night?</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62d680439a79476eb2afeac9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 02:10:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62d680439a79476eb2afeac9/</guid><description>Melatonin is the most common sleep drug that can be found in pharmacies around the world and as a dietary supplement: it is available in tablets, dragées, capsules, drops, and even in the form of gummy bears. It is a natural remedy in the sense that melatonin from medical preparations is no different from the one produced by the body itself. And it really triggers sleep. But does it follow that a melatonin pill will help you get rid of insomnia?</description></item><item><title>From $26.5 billion to $1: how Sam Bankman-Fried conquered the crypto world and lost everything</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6376576c9a7947568646d4b9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 01:56:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6376576c9a7947568646d4b9/</guid><description>The billionaire, the “golden boy” of the crypto industry, the owner of the successful FTX exchange - all this until recently referred to Sam Bankman-Fried, famous enough to get by with the initials SBF.
But in November, his position changed dramatically : he left the post of CEO of FTX and began bankruptcy proceedings (along with Alameda Research and 130 other partner companies), and his fortune was destroyed after the fall in the value of FTX&amp;rsquo;s business to $1.</description></item><item><title>How to raise children correctly: Musk, Bezos, Gates, Branson answer</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62c816859a794734a1a1d2ab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 12:05:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62c816859a794734a1a1d2ab/</guid><description>Elon Musk Tesla founder Elon Musk has seven children: triplets Damian, Saxon and Kai and twins Griffin and Xavier from his first marriage. In 2020, the head of SpaceX Elon Musk and singer Grimes had a son, who was given the unusual name Ex Ash A-Twelv (X Æ A-12), and in 2022, a daughter, Exa Dark Syderil (abbreviated her name sounds Y). Musk&amp;rsquo;s first child from his marriage to his first wife, Justine Wilson, son Nevada, died at the age of ten weeks from sudden infant death syndrome.</description></item><item><title>The Illusion of Anxiety: How the Mind Makes a Person Worry for No Reason</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ff57e9a7947122a8e0b67/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 02:10:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ff57e9a7947122a8e0b67/</guid><description>Excerpt from Amy Johnson&amp;rsquo;s Toxic Thoughts. How to stop dwelling on the negative and calm the mind, MIF publishing house.
I learned to worry at an early age.
Mom often worried out loud, but I did not understand that she was worried about things that were not in reality. As a child, this is impossible to understand.
We&amp;rsquo;re running out of money. We will have to eat only canned soups for dinner.</description></item><item><title>Amendments for applicants for Golden Visas in the UAE: what they change</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6373be209a7947fb386fc99a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 14:59:40 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6373be209a7947fb386fc99a/</guid><description>Over the past couple of years, the demand for real estate in Dubai and in the UAE as a whole has grown significantly. Investors from all over the world have turned their eyes to the country, and the Russians are confidently among the ten most active of them - the neutral status of the Emirates in the current geopolitical situation played an important role here.
According to the Dubai Land Department, the third quarter of this year broke another record, becoming the most productive in history: more than 25.</description></item><item><title>There are strikes in the EU over wages. How will this affect corporate profits?</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6375071a9a79476e9270960a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:14:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6375071a9a79476e9270960a/</guid><description>In 2022, Europe&amp;rsquo;s largest companies are facing record inflation and the worst energy crisis in 40 years. Now corporations are preparing for new challenges.
Against the backdrop of inflation, the purchasing power of the population is falling, and workers are demanding higher salaries. Despite the fact that many European companies are experiencing a shortage of qualified personnel, not all firms are ready to accommodate employees, fearing that this will negatively affect the financial performance of the companies themselves.</description></item><item><title>How not to bring a business to a new market: top 10 mistakes of founders</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6374da319a794759335972d6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:10:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6374da319a794759335972d6/</guid><description>In recent months, Russian entrepreneurs have had to rethink their approaches to scaling abroad. Companies have shifted their focus from Western markets to other areas, such as Turkey, the United Arab Emirates, Latin America, and the CIS countries. Although these regions are no less promising, the founders often make the same mistakes that prevent them from gaining a foothold in new countries.
1. Fear of emerging markets Before February 2022, entrepreneurs tended to consider Europe and the US as target markets when scaling overseas.</description></item><item><title>Should children be banned from playing video games?</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6375e9309a794723491524f4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:06:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6375e9309a794723491524f4/</guid><description>The average adult spends about seven hours in front of gadget screens, children and teenagers spend four to six hours. In addition to working at a computer, people watch TV or video on a smartphone, read e-books, communicate in social networks, play a console. For many, gaming becomes a profession: some develop video games, while others compete with each other for prizes of several million dollars.
But, despite the prevalence of gadgets and games, they are treated with caution in society.</description></item><item><title>How to instill in a child a love of sports and how this will help him in life</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636223429a7947a88809bb39/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 14:49:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636223429a7947a88809bb39/</guid><description>Physical activity is just as necessary for people as good nutrition and sleep. From birth, human development is associated with movement. It helps to improve sensory perception, to know your body, to learn the skills of large and fine motor skills, to form immunity. Thanks to physical activity, the child actively learns the world around him, develops intellectually and psychologically.
The importance of physical development began to speak in the era of humanism (XIV-XVI century).</description></item><item><title>What economic theory caused the global recession</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6374e1769a79475cdbaaa663/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 14:13:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6374e1769a79475cdbaaa663/</guid><description>Modern Monetary Theory (CMT) is a relatively new approach to economic regulation. It appeared in the early 1990s and suggests that the state can issue a sovereign currency without regard to negative factors for the economy.
Supporters of the MMT claim that, if properly regulated, an increase in the money supply will not cause inflation and a deterioration in the economic condition of the country. However, in practice it turned out that the theory does not work as its adherents expected.</description></item><item><title>Will genetic tests help you choose a diet and sport</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63578cac9a7947a5bbc41bee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:48:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63578cac9a7947a5bbc41bee/</guid><description>The first thing a person who decides to undergo genetic testing faces is the variety of offers from different companies. They can be divided into two large groups: diagnostic and screening.
1. Diagnostic tests are prescribed by a doctor when it is necessary to establish an accurate diagnosis. Usually, such a study is required if the external manifestations of the disease do not fit into the textbook clinical picture of a particular hereditary syndrome.</description></item><item><title>How users and advertisers are fleeing Twitter Elon Musk</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6373b4299a7947f7e5f6fd65/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:38:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6373b4299a7947f7e5f6fd65/</guid><description>The drama surrounding the Elon Musk-Twitter deal seemed to be over with the final agreement between the parties. However, it turned out that everything was just beginning: the new owner began to radically rebuild the work of the social network, look for additional sources of funding and argue with politicians, officials, advertisers and ordinary users.
Disappointed with Musk&amp;rsquo;s actions, Twitter users began to look for an alternative to the social network.</description></item><item><title>Why the Japanese economy is falling again and what will happen to it next</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63738f8b9a7947e7e6442c83/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:22:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63738f8b9a7947e7e6442c83/</guid><description>The Japanese economy, the third largest in the world, unexpectedly showed a fall in July-September after nine months of steady growth. Despite the easing of covid restrictions, the country&amp;rsquo;s GDP was negatively affected by the depreciation of the national currency, rising prices for goods and services, as well as the risks of a global recession.
The economy contracted by 1.2% in annual terms (analysts had expected growth of 1.1%), falling compared to the previous three-month period amounted to 0.</description></item><item><title>Employees flee from energy giant ExxonMobil. What's Happening - Bloomberg</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636d239c9a7947b439cfe59d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 17:49:41 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636d239c9a7947b439cfe59d/</guid><description>ExxonMobil, an oil and gas company with a century and a half history, not only survived corporate upheavals and global crises, but also strengthened its position. Thanks to rising oil prices, Exxon shares have risen in price by 72% over the year, to $112 a share. This is an absolute historical maximum. The capitalization of the company is $456 billion, which makes it the largest oil and gas company in America and one of the leaders in the oil sector in the world.</description></item><item><title>Fashion designer Ralph Lauren: “I prepared for greatness from an early age”</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e3be69a79470810a89a6c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 15:38:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e3be69a79470810a89a6c/</guid><description>About a dreamer from the Bronx A student of one of the New York schools, Ralph Lifshitz, wrote in his graduation album in 1957 that he was going to become a millionaire, although at that time he did not even think how he would achieve this. Today, the whole world knows him as Ralph Lauren, and he clearly over fulfilled his plan: his fortune is estimated at $6.5 billion. Lauren&amp;rsquo;s business empire includes several lines of clothing, shoes and accessories, a brand of furniture and home goods, as well as several restaurants.</description></item><item><title>The Chinese market is finally growing. What pushes it up and how long will it last</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63723eb69a79477bbacfcc87/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 15:17:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63723eb69a79477bbacfcc87/</guid><description>Chinese stocks jumped sharply during the trading session on Friday on the back of easing domestic anti-covid restrictions and encouraging US inflation data. The rally continued in trading on Monday, this time under the influence of promises of new measures to support Chinese developers from the government.
In total, over the two trading days, the Hang Seng index added 9.5% and reached 17619.72 points, CSI 300 - 3794.0171 points (+2.94%), Hang Seng Tech - 3554.</description></item><item><title>The world is facing a wave of corporate fraud. How to spot cheaters</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637236619a7947775e953925/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 15:11:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637236619a7947775e953925/</guid><description>Ten months after the U.S. stock market hit its latest all-time high, big tech stocks have suffered yet another decline. Hopes that the US Federal Reserve would change course did not come true: the increase in interest rates would be more serious than previously thought. The bond market is signaling the onset of a recession. Could it be worse? Of course yes. Boosting periods in the stock market, such as the one that peaked in January, are usually accompanied by an increase in fraud.</description></item><item><title>“This is very, very bad for the crypto industry.” Who will be dragged to the bottom by the collapse of FTX</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264d99a79478caba1a753/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:34:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264d99a79478caba1a753/</guid><description>The echoes of the powerful collapse of FTX are still being felt in the crypto industry. On Monday, the value of digital currencies fell again as the market situation worsened over the weekend.
Some in the industry have said that the fall of FTX was &amp;ldquo;Lehman&amp;rsquo;s moment&amp;rdquo;, drawing parallels to the collapse of the investment bank in 2008, which was the starting point of the global crisis. The founder of Binance agreed with this metaphor, saying that comparing the current turmoil in the cryptocurrency market with the 2008 global financial crisis is an exact analogy.</description></item><item><title>Why squiggles and sticking out tongue help you focus</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63622aa49a7947a9e99aa406/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:30:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63622aa49a7947a9e99aa406/</guid><description>An excerpt from Jen Martin&amp;rsquo;s book It&amp;rsquo;s Just Me. How science explains our oddities and habits, Alpina Publisher.
Why do I stick out my tongue to focus? The next time you see a baby who is doing something intently with his hands, follow him. Most likely, his tongue will stick out. Is it just a cute baby trait or something more?
Think about how you yourself do things that require precise movements, such as threading a needle or getting ready to send a billiard ball into a pocket.</description></item><item><title>Unreliable person: how the head of FTX lost $16 billion in a matter of days</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264559a79478c20090632/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 17:29:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264559a79478c20090632/</guid><description>FTX, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest centralized cryptocurrency exchanges, was valued at $32 billion in early 2022. The company was backed by well-known investors including US giants BlackRock and Tiger Global, Japanese investment bank SoftBank, and Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest pension fund, Ontario Teachers&amp;rsquo; Pension Plan.
At its peak, FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried was worth an estimated $26 billion. He earned a reputation as a “crypto savior” in the digital asset market. In the summer of 2022, after the collapse of the cryptocurrency market, Bankman-Fried actively supported crypto companies that found themselves in a difficult financial situation.</description></item><item><title>Six healthy habits of tennis player Anastasia Pivovarova</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635fa4b69a79476ff47251db/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 15:55:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635fa4b69a79476ff47251db/</guid><description>The endless scrolling of the news feed and the widespread instability increase the level of anxiety. But over the years of my sports career, I realized one thing: if you can’t avoid stress, and you can’t change your perception, you need to transform your routine. I will tell you about what helps me maintain mental health.
Daily Meditations According to a study by scientists from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, people who practice meditation are more resistant to stress than others.</description></item><item><title>The United States recognized Russia as a “country with a non-market economy.” What does it mean</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e4ff99a794711b44c0b3b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 08:59:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e4ff99a794711b44c0b3b/</guid><description>The US Department of Commerce announced Thursday that it has changed the status of the Russian economy from &amp;ldquo;market&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;non-market.&amp;rdquo; The move is aimed at further reducing bilateral trade and isolating Russia amid ongoing geopolitical tensions, experts say.
The decision follows a significant increase in Moscow&amp;rsquo;s interference in economic activity since the beginning of last year, the ministry said. This introduced an imbalance in the work of the sphere of foreign exchange markets, labor relations and foreign investment.</description></item><item><title>End of an Era: Will Social Media Stocks Stop Rising?</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e00579a7947eb973f2807/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 09:38:30 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e00579a7947eb973f2807/</guid><description>This year has led to a record drop in social media stocks. Meta shares (recognized as extremist and banned in Russia) have fallen by 73% since the beginning of the year, to the level of early 2016, showing the worst dynamics among all securities of the S &amp;amp; P 500 index. If last summer the company&amp;rsquo;s capitalization reached $1 trillion, then in November 2022 it was about $240 billion. Back in October 2021, Meta co-founder Mark Zuckerberg was the third-richest person in the world, and now he has moved to 29th place.</description></item><item><title>Republicans win congressional elections. What does this mean for the economy</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636ba9409a7947373bd99e7f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 09:20:07 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636ba9409a7947373bd99e7f/</guid><description>This year&amp;rsquo;s midterm elections are marked by particular economic and political vulnerability in the United States. Inflation that persists despite all the efforts of regulators, a more than 50% chance of a recession, the pressure of rising interest rates and the expectation of further geopolitical escalation make not only the American but also the world community closely monitor the voting results.
The elections will determine the composition of Congress, which has the authority to develop fiscal policy, trade with foreign countries and regulate the public debt.</description></item><item><title>“It’s all about concentration”: Robert Downey Jr. on Wing Chun</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636a3c039a794747e4e95bcf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:27:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636a3c039a794747e4e95bcf/</guid><description>During his career, 57-year-old American actor Robert Downey Jr. has starred in more than 70 films. He has won two Golden Globe Awards in 2001 and 2010. He also received several Oscar nominations. Downey Jr. has been on the Forbes list of Hollywood&amp;rsquo;s highest-paid actors four times, while topping the list three times.
But in the life of Downey Jr. there was a black streak. In 1992, at the age of 27, Downey played Charlie Chaplin in the film Chaplin and was named one of the most talented actors of the 1990s.</description></item><item><title>Four Ways to Reduce Corruption in a Company</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6363883c9a79472075a6fa59/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 14:57:05 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6363883c9a79472075a6fa59/</guid><description>Despite the deal with the investigation, participants in the corruption scheme may be held criminally liable. The reason is that such behavior in state bodies and business is unacceptable.
Example: Boris Shpigel, the head of Biotek, who was accused of giving a bribe to the governor of the Penza region, said in the Moscow City Court that he would actively cooperate with the investigation. However, the court refused to leave him under house arrest and placed him in custody.</description></item><item><title>Five habits that will help you live longer</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635942059a79473ddeadb282/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 11:13:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635942059a79473ddeadb282/</guid><description>Eternal life is a question that has worried the best minds of mankind throughout history. What people have not tried to prolong their existence for at least a few years: from bathing in the blood of a deer to freezing in cryogenic chambers. Dystopias about immortal existence beat all records of popularity, and the younger generation is fond of vampires and elves, who are also endowed with this gift, according to the fiction of the writers.</description></item><item><title>“Why are we so poor?”: how to answer uncomfortable questions from a child</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62e774329a7947a74bc87a9d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 11:51:30 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62e774329a7947a74bc87a9d/</guid><description>Telling a child why it rains is much easier than telling a child where babies come from. Scions sometimes ask about things that seem inappropriate to us, and we cannot find a suitable explanation. Some parents, blushing and turning pale, begin to invent a &amp;ldquo;politically correct&amp;rdquo; version. Others brush off the on-duty phrase: &amp;ldquo;Grow up - you will know.&amp;rdquo; But there are those who clearly and calmly explain everything to the child, without making him feel uncomfortable.</description></item><item><title>Eight effective ways to add physical activity to your life</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634fb0ae9a794778c18fbec2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 11:28:06 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634fb0ae9a794778c18fbec2/</guid><description>Only one in five Russians walks 10,000 steps a day, an approximate amount needed to maintain heart tone and well-being. This result was shown by a survey of CDEK and the Guldog service. At the same time, almost a third of respondents walk less than 5 thousand steps a day, of which 11% do not even fulfill the minimum bar of 3 thousand steps.
Our study confirms these findings: more than a third of the participants admitted that they lead a passive lifestyle.</description></item><item><title>Tea and Paper Newspaper: How Google CEO Sundar Pichai Starts the Day</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636234309a7947ae4b67e1b7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 02:38:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636234309a7947ae4b67e1b7/</guid><description>An Indian-born metallurgical engineer and cricket enthusiast, Sundar Pichai has led Google since 2015. In December 2019, he was appointed head of parent company Alphabet, which under his leadership became the fourth major technology corporation with a market value of more than $1 trillion.
The position requires Pichai to be able to multitask. Nevertheless, despite the high load, it works calmly, measuredly and without fuss. In this he is helped by morning rituals, with which he begins every day.</description></item><item><title>“I’m very busy”: how feeling constantly busy destroys life</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6363a7719a79472ee06e59b7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 02:49:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6363a7719a79472ee06e59b7/</guid><description>The day of a modern person is full of different tasks to the eyeballs. Trips to the office, work, gym, walking the dog, cooking, cleaning, visiting the doctor. It seems that you will never be able to cross off all the tasks from the to-do list. “I wish there were more hours in the day!” - this is the phrase that many people often end the day with.
Scientists call this state of haste time poverty.</description></item><item><title>Sober billionaires: Buffett, Rybakov, Durov - about giving up alcohol</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635a6cbd9a7947127de2ddcc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 14:34:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635a6cbd9a7947127de2ddcc/</guid><description>Igor Rybakov “When I came to university, alcohol was disgusting to me. More precisely, I was neutral to him. But what happened among the students at the university? Well, there, let&amp;rsquo;s try beer there, and so on &amp;hellip; And then what happened? Well, I began to apply a little beer, then more, more, ” recalled the co-founder of TechnoNIKOL. Now Rybakov is convinced that alcohol, like drugs, is a way to distract from difficulties and drown out stress, which only delays the solution of problems and thereby exacerbates them.</description></item><item><title>The United States began a technological blockade of China. Where it leads</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635140999a79477c641cd6b2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:52:30 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635140999a79477c641cd6b2/</guid><description>Competition between the world&amp;rsquo;s two largest economies, the United States and China, is intensifying on the technology front. Before the landmark 20th Congress of the Communist Party of China, the Joe Biden administration announced serious new restrictions on the sale of semiconductor technologies to China.
The new measures from the US Department of Commerce are largely aimed at slowing down the development of Chinese military programs. In their technology, they use supercomputers to simulate nuclear explosions, control hypersonic weapons and create advanced networks to monitor political dissenters and minorities, writes The New York Times.</description></item><item><title>The burden of abuse: “toxic” leadership is experiencing a new flowering in Russia</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63502ac69a7947290202fd49/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 15:04:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63502ac69a7947290202fd49/</guid><description>Due to the crisis, many Russian companies found themselves on the brink of survival. On the one hand, circumstances require a firm hand, on the other hand, many managers even in calm times could not boast of managerial competencies, and tough management is completely confused with rudeness. “Team leaders faced a difficult task: to maintain efficiency and effectiveness in order to create results, despite external turbulence. This is not easy for everyone,” admits Daria Korobkova, team coach, business mentor, managing partner of the TeamSonance consulting company.</description></item><item><title>“The worst is yet to come”: why economists consider a US recession inevitable</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ea5049a79472ea711b05a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 14:22:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ea5049a79472ea711b05a/</guid><description>Discussions about the likelihood of a recession in the world&amp;rsquo;s largest economy have been going on for several months. The new forecast of experts seems to be able to put an end to these conversations: in their opinion, a recession will come in the next 12 months, and it is not possible to avoid this scenario.
A recession is a significant decline in business activity that lasts for months or even years.</description></item><item><title>How to persevere in difficult times. Developing antifragility</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634524a29a794701ac1ebef4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 15:03:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634524a29a794701ac1ebef4/</guid><description>Economist and trader Nassim Taleb originally coined the term &amp;ldquo;antifragile&amp;rdquo; to describe various economic or social systems. However, over the two pandemic years, this term has become hype. Therefore, today it is often applied at organizational, team and individual levels.
Personal antifragility is the ability of a person to capitalize on failure and loss; harden when faced with chaos or blows of fate.
How to become antifragile?
1. Choose the right field for the game I propose to look at the dramatic circumstances through the logotherapeutic model of Fate-Freedom, which Viktor Frankl laid the foundation for his practice.</description></item><item><title>Student time management: how to teach children to plan things</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/633c47e29a7947b8898ef22a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 11:22:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/633c47e29a7947b8898ef22a/</guid><description>From the book Time Management for Children. How to have time to study and relax” by Marianna Lukashenko, publishing house “Alpina Publisher”
Learning to share things The main contribution to the employment of the child is made, of course, by the school. We as well-meaning parents are also trying to keep our child busy. At the same time, we are guided by two motives: when a child is small, it is important for us to develop him, and when older - &amp;ldquo;to keep busy, so that he does not hang out just like that and does not engage in nonsense.</description></item><item><title>How to raise a child to school or kindergarten without screaming and panic: 7 tips</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6315c7489a794736cdcc6e41/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 11:41:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6315c7489a794736cdcc6e41/</guid><description>School has begun, which means that deadlines have appeared not only for adults, but also for children. And as if the parents got the moral right to push and demand from them to meet the timing. Of course, it is important to come to school or kindergarten on time. But the ways to achieve this goal can take unpleasant forms. We begin to raise our voices, threaten, criticize and punish. Let&amp;rsquo;s try to figure out how to organize the morning so as not to kill each other and come to work, school or kindergarten in a good mood.</description></item><item><title>How parental behavior affects the future of children</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/630f07249a794733f65b94f5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 11:46:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/630f07249a794733f65b94f5/</guid><description>Each parent imagines success and implementation criteria in their own way. For some, it is important that a child in his adult life could achieve his goals, be active, receive social recognition and a high social status. For some, the main thing is that he is able to unleash the potential inherent in him and enjoy the chosen activity.
The scope, boundaries and meanings of &amp;ldquo;success&amp;rdquo; depend both on the individuality of a person and on the historical era in which he lives.</description></item><item><title>What behavior should be excluded by adults in order to develop leadership in children</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62cc1d939a7947409458b87f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:35:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62cc1d939a7947409458b87f/</guid><description>Today, children from a very young age observe a huge number of examples in social networks, when people who seem to have made no effort to become famous and famous become famous. Moreover, they may not have the qualities that are commonly believed needed to manage and maintain their popularity. Quick and easy popularity often ends just as quickly, and a person can find himself on his own, without the necessary education and without having formed the qualities necessary for adulthood.</description></item><item><title>Your disputes with a teenager end in scandals. What are you doing wrong</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62aaf7b69a79471e581561a2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:30:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62aaf7b69a79471e581561a2/</guid><description>If you have a teenager in your house, then you may have noticed how difficult it can be for him to cope with emotions. Ten minutes ago, he completely agreed with you, and now he contradicts everything, screams and pours accusations. It happens differently: a teenager, on the contrary, silently walks away from the conversation, holding a grudge in himself. Both situations can lead to conflict, and from my experience I can say that they happen quite often.</description></item><item><title>How to tear a child away from a smartphone and whether it should be done</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/630370e79a7947a8b4e3bfd3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 12:24:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/630370e79a7947a8b4e3bfd3/</guid><description>We live in a world where electronic devices are everywhere. They make our lives easier, such as helping us find information and pay bills faster and more conveniently. They also give us a lot of positive emotions from communicating with friends and family, watching interesting films, listening to our favorite music. Many parents, however, are frightened by the fact that their children sit in front of screens for too long, and it can be extremely difficult to captivate them with something else.</description></item></channel></rss>