<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ilya Rozov on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/ilya-rozov/</link><description>Recent content in Ilya Rozov on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:30:47 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/ilya-rozov/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Your disputes with a teenager end in scandals. What are you doing wrong</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62aaf7b69a79471e581561a2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:30:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62aaf7b69a79471e581561a2/</guid><description>If you have a teenager in your house, then you may have noticed how difficult it can be for him to cope with emotions. Ten minutes ago, he completely agreed with you, and now he contradicts everything, screams and pours accusations. It happens differently: a teenager, on the contrary, silently walks away from the conversation, holding a grudge in himself. Both situations can lead to conflict, and from my experience I can say that they happen quite often.</description></item><item><title>How to tear a child away from a smartphone and whether it should be done</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/630370e79a7947a8b4e3bfd3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 12:24:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/630370e79a7947a8b4e3bfd3/</guid><description>We live in a world where electronic devices are everywhere. They make our lives easier, such as helping us find information and pay bills faster and more conveniently. They also give us a lot of positive emotions from communicating with friends and family, watching interesting films, listening to our favorite music. Many parents, however, are frightened by the fact that their children sit in front of screens for too long, and it can be extremely difficult to captivate them with something else.</description></item></channel></rss>