<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Forecasts on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/forecasts/</link><description>Recent content in Forecasts on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 14:59:40 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/forecasts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amendments for applicants for Golden Visas in the UAE: what they change</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6373be209a7947fb386fc99a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 14:59:40 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6373be209a7947fb386fc99a/</guid><description>Over the past couple of years, the demand for real estate in Dubai and in the UAE as a whole has grown significantly. Investors from all over the world have turned their eyes to the country, and the Russians are confidently among the ten most active of them - the neutral status of the Emirates in the current geopolitical situation played an important role here.
According to the Dubai Land Department, the third quarter of this year broke another record, becoming the most productive in history: more than 25.</description></item><item><title>“This is very, very bad for the crypto industry.” Who will be dragged to the bottom by the collapse of FTX</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264d99a79478caba1a753/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:34:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264d99a79478caba1a753/</guid><description>The echoes of the powerful collapse of FTX are still being felt in the crypto industry. On Monday, the value of digital currencies fell again as the market situation worsened over the weekend.
Some in the industry have said that the fall of FTX was &amp;ldquo;Lehman&amp;rsquo;s moment&amp;rdquo;, drawing parallels to the collapse of the investment bank in 2008, which was the starting point of the global crisis. The founder of Binance agreed with this metaphor, saying that comparing the current turmoil in the cryptocurrency market with the 2008 global financial crisis is an exact analogy.</description></item><item><title>Republicans win congressional elections. What does this mean for the economy</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636ba9409a7947373bd99e7f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 09:20:07 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636ba9409a7947373bd99e7f/</guid><description>This year&amp;rsquo;s midterm elections are marked by particular economic and political vulnerability in the United States. Inflation that persists despite all the efforts of regulators, a more than 50% chance of a recession, the pressure of rising interest rates and the expectation of further geopolitical escalation make not only the American but also the world community closely monitor the voting results.
The elections will determine the composition of Congress, which has the authority to develop fiscal policy, trade with foreign countries and regulate the public debt.</description></item><item><title>“The worst is yet to come”: why economists consider a US recession inevitable</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ea5049a79472ea711b05a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 14:22:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ea5049a79472ea711b05a/</guid><description>Discussions about the likelihood of a recession in the world&amp;rsquo;s largest economy have been going on for several months. The new forecast of experts seems to be able to put an end to these conversations: in their opinion, a recession will come in the next 12 months, and it is not possible to avoid this scenario.
A recession is a significant decline in business activity that lasts for months or even years.</description></item></channel></rss>