<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Corporate culture on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/corporate-culture/</link><description>Recent content in Corporate culture on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:26:29 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/corporate-culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Extroverts and lazy people with high salaries: how Twitter lived before Musk</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63774a499a7947963c0c3f14/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:26:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63774a499a7947963c0c3f14/</guid><description>In early November, a photo of a woman in a sleeping bag and a sleep mask on the floor of an office building went viral on Twitter. “When you need something from your Twitter boss Elon,” Twitter product manager Evan Jones captioned the picture. Twitter director of product management Esther Crawford, who was the lead, commented: &amp;ldquo;When your team is working around the clock to meet a deadline, you sleep at work.</description></item><item><title>Employees flee from energy giant ExxonMobil. What's Happening - Bloomberg</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636d239c9a7947b439cfe59d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 17:49:41 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636d239c9a7947b439cfe59d/</guid><description>ExxonMobil, an oil and gas company with a century and a half history, not only survived corporate upheavals and global crises, but also strengthened its position. Thanks to rising oil prices, Exxon shares have risen in price by 72% over the year, to $112 a share. This is an absolute historical maximum. The capitalization of the company is $456 billion, which makes it the largest oil and gas company in America and one of the leaders in the oil sector in the world.</description></item></channel></rss>