<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Anna Vasiltsova on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/anna-vasiltsova/</link><description>Recent content in Anna Vasiltsova on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 01:56:21 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/anna-vasiltsova/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From $26.5 billion to $1: how Sam Bankman-Fried conquered the crypto world and lost everything</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6376576c9a7947568646d4b9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 01:56:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6376576c9a7947568646d4b9/</guid><description>The billionaire, the “golden boy” of the crypto industry, the owner of the successful FTX exchange - all this until recently referred to Sam Bankman-Fried, famous enough to get by with the initials SBF.
But in November, his position changed dramatically : he left the post of CEO of FTX and began bankruptcy proceedings (along with Alameda Research and 130 other partner companies), and his fortune was destroyed after the fall in the value of FTX&amp;rsquo;s business to $1.</description></item><item><title>Why the Japanese economy is falling again and what will happen to it next</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63738f8b9a7947e7e6442c83/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:22:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63738f8b9a7947e7e6442c83/</guid><description>The Japanese economy, the third largest in the world, unexpectedly showed a fall in July-September after nine months of steady growth. Despite the easing of covid restrictions, the country&amp;rsquo;s GDP was negatively affected by the depreciation of the national currency, rising prices for goods and services, as well as the risks of a global recession.
The economy contracted by 1.2% in annual terms (analysts had expected growth of 1.1%), falling compared to the previous three-month period amounted to 0.</description></item><item><title>The Chinese market is finally growing. What pushes it up and how long will it last</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63723eb69a79477bbacfcc87/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 15:17:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63723eb69a79477bbacfcc87/</guid><description>Chinese stocks jumped sharply during the trading session on Friday on the back of easing domestic anti-covid restrictions and encouraging US inflation data. The rally continued in trading on Monday, this time under the influence of promises of new measures to support Chinese developers from the government.
In total, over the two trading days, the Hang Seng index added 9.5% and reached 17619.72 points, CSI 300 - 3794.0171 points (+2.94%), Hang Seng Tech - 3554.</description></item><item><title>The United States recognized Russia as a “country with a non-market economy.” What does it mean</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e4ff99a794711b44c0b3b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 08:59:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e4ff99a794711b44c0b3b/</guid><description>The US Department of Commerce announced Thursday that it has changed the status of the Russian economy from &amp;ldquo;market&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;non-market.&amp;rdquo; The move is aimed at further reducing bilateral trade and isolating Russia amid ongoing geopolitical tensions, experts say.
The decision follows a significant increase in Moscow&amp;rsquo;s interference in economic activity since the beginning of last year, the ministry said. This introduced an imbalance in the work of the sphere of foreign exchange markets, labor relations and foreign investment.</description></item><item><title>Republicans win congressional elections. What does this mean for the economy</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636ba9409a7947373bd99e7f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 09:20:07 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636ba9409a7947373bd99e7f/</guid><description>This year&amp;rsquo;s midterm elections are marked by particular economic and political vulnerability in the United States. Inflation that persists despite all the efforts of regulators, a more than 50% chance of a recession, the pressure of rising interest rates and the expectation of further geopolitical escalation make not only the American but also the world community closely monitor the voting results.
The elections will determine the composition of Congress, which has the authority to develop fiscal policy, trade with foreign countries and regulate the public debt.</description></item><item><title>“The worst is yet to come”: why economists consider a US recession inevitable</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ea5049a79472ea711b05a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 14:22:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ea5049a79472ea711b05a/</guid><description>Discussions about the likelihood of a recession in the world&amp;rsquo;s largest economy have been going on for several months. The new forecast of experts seems to be able to put an end to these conversations: in their opinion, a recession will come in the next 12 months, and it is not possible to avoid this scenario.
A recession is a significant decline in business activity that lasts for months or even years.</description></item></channel></rss>