<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Self-development on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/interest/self-development/</link><description>Recent content in Self-development on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 15:38:36 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/interest/self-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fashion designer Ralph Lauren: “I prepared for greatness from an early age”</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e3be69a79470810a89a6c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 15:38:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e3be69a79470810a89a6c/</guid><description>About a dreamer from the Bronx A student of one of the New York schools, Ralph Lifshitz, wrote in his graduation album in 1957 that he was going to become a millionaire, although at that time he did not even think how he would achieve this. Today, the whole world knows him as Ralph Lauren, and he clearly over fulfilled his plan: his fortune is estimated at $6.5 billion. Lauren&amp;rsquo;s business empire includes several lines of clothing, shoes and accessories, a brand of furniture and home goods, as well as several restaurants.</description></item><item><title>How to persevere in difficult times. Developing antifragility</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634524a29a794701ac1ebef4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 15:03:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634524a29a794701ac1ebef4/</guid><description>Economist and trader Nassim Taleb originally coined the term &amp;ldquo;antifragile&amp;rdquo; to describe various economic or social systems. However, over the two pandemic years, this term has become hype. Therefore, today it is often applied at organizational, team and individual levels.
Personal antifragility is the ability of a person to capitalize on failure and loss; harden when faced with chaos or blows of fate.
How to become antifragile?
1. Choose the right field for the game I propose to look at the dramatic circumstances through the logotherapeutic model of Fate-Freedom, which Viktor Frankl laid the foundation for his practice.</description></item><item><title>What behavior should be excluded by adults in order to develop leadership in children</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62cc1d939a7947409458b87f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:35:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62cc1d939a7947409458b87f/</guid><description>Today, children from a very young age observe a huge number of examples in social networks, when people who seem to have made no effort to become famous and famous become famous. Moreover, they may not have the qualities that are commonly believed needed to manage and maintain their popularity. Quick and easy popularity often ends just as quickly, and a person can find himself on his own, without the necessary education and without having formed the qualities necessary for adulthood.</description></item></channel></rss>