<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nick Lukhminsky on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/nick-lukhminsky/</link><description>Recent content in Nick Lukhminsky on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 01:54:04 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/nick-lukhminsky/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why did the US start having problems with payments on car loans</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63777c999a7947ad48fb2802/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 01:54:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63777c999a7947ad48fb2802/</guid><description>The increase in the key rate in the US has now hit car owners who bought cars on credit. Interest rates on loans have risen, and inflation has significantly reduced the purchasing power of consumers. As a result, payment discipline among borrowers has shaken in the United States.
But the problem lies not only in unscrupulous car owners. Car prices also began to decline, and this led to a new round of problems.</description></item><item><title>What economic theory caused the global recession</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6374e1769a79475cdbaaa663/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 14:13:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6374e1769a79475cdbaaa663/</guid><description>Modern Monetary Theory (CMT) is a relatively new approach to economic regulation. It appeared in the early 1990s and suggests that the state can issue a sovereign currency without regard to negative factors for the economy.
Supporters of the MMT claim that, if properly regulated, an increase in the money supply will not cause inflation and a deterioration in the economic condition of the country. However, in practice it turned out that the theory does not work as its adherents expected.</description></item><item><title>How users and advertisers are fleeing Twitter Elon Musk</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6373b4299a7947f7e5f6fd65/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:38:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6373b4299a7947f7e5f6fd65/</guid><description>The drama surrounding the Elon Musk-Twitter deal seemed to be over with the final agreement between the parties. However, it turned out that everything was just beginning: the new owner began to radically rebuild the work of the social network, look for additional sources of funding and argue with politicians, officials, advertisers and ordinary users.
Disappointed with Musk&amp;rsquo;s actions, Twitter users began to look for an alternative to the social network.</description></item></channel></rss>