<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mindfulness on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/mindfulness/</link><description>Recent content in mindfulness on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 02:10:37 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/mindfulness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Illusion of Anxiety: How the Mind Makes a Person Worry for No Reason</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ff57e9a7947122a8e0b67/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 02:10:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ff57e9a7947122a8e0b67/</guid><description>Excerpt from Amy Johnson&amp;rsquo;s Toxic Thoughts. How to stop dwelling on the negative and calm the mind, MIF publishing house.
I learned to worry at an early age.
Mom often worried out loud, but I did not understand that she was worried about things that were not in reality. As a child, this is impossible to understand.
We&amp;rsquo;re running out of money. We will have to eat only canned soups for dinner.</description></item><item><title>Six healthy habits of tennis player Anastasia Pivovarova</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635fa4b69a79476ff47251db/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 15:55:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635fa4b69a79476ff47251db/</guid><description>The endless scrolling of the news feed and the widespread instability increase the level of anxiety. But over the years of my sports career, I realized one thing: if you can’t avoid stress, and you can’t change your perception, you need to transform your routine. I will tell you about what helps me maintain mental health.
Daily Meditations According to a study by scientists from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, people who practice meditation are more resistant to stress than others.</description></item><item><title>“I’m very busy”: how feeling constantly busy destroys life</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6363a7719a79472ee06e59b7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 02:49:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6363a7719a79472ee06e59b7/</guid><description>The day of a modern person is full of different tasks to the eyeballs. Trips to the office, work, gym, walking the dog, cooking, cleaning, visiting the doctor. It seems that you will never be able to cross off all the tasks from the to-do list. “I wish there were more hours in the day!” - this is the phrase that many people often end the day with.
Scientists call this state of haste time poverty.</description></item></channel></rss>