<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stock on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/stock/</link><description>Recent content in Stock on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 14:13:01 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/stock/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What economic theory caused the global recession</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6374e1769a79475cdbaaa663/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 14:13:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6374e1769a79475cdbaaa663/</guid><description>Modern Monetary Theory (CMT) is a relatively new approach to economic regulation. It appeared in the early 1990s and suggests that the state can issue a sovereign currency without regard to negative factors for the economy.
Supporters of the MMT claim that, if properly regulated, an increase in the money supply will not cause inflation and a deterioration in the economic condition of the country. However, in practice it turned out that the theory does not work as its adherents expected.</description></item><item><title>How users and advertisers are fleeing Twitter Elon Musk</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6373b4299a7947f7e5f6fd65/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:38:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6373b4299a7947f7e5f6fd65/</guid><description>The drama surrounding the Elon Musk-Twitter deal seemed to be over with the final agreement between the parties. However, it turned out that everything was just beginning: the new owner began to radically rebuild the work of the social network, look for additional sources of funding and argue with politicians, officials, advertisers and ordinary users.
Disappointed with Musk&amp;rsquo;s actions, Twitter users began to look for an alternative to the social network.</description></item><item><title>The Chinese market is finally growing. What pushes it up and how long will it last</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63723eb69a79477bbacfcc87/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 15:17:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63723eb69a79477bbacfcc87/</guid><description>Chinese stocks jumped sharply during the trading session on Friday on the back of easing domestic anti-covid restrictions and encouraging US inflation data. The rally continued in trading on Monday, this time under the influence of promises of new measures to support Chinese developers from the government.
In total, over the two trading days, the Hang Seng index added 9.5% and reached 17619.72 points, CSI 300 - 3794.0171 points (+2.94%), Hang Seng Tech - 3554.</description></item><item><title>End of an Era: Will Social Media Stocks Stop Rising?</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e00579a7947eb973f2807/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 09:38:30 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e00579a7947eb973f2807/</guid><description>This year has led to a record drop in social media stocks. Meta shares (recognized as extremist and banned in Russia) have fallen by 73% since the beginning of the year, to the level of early 2016, showing the worst dynamics among all securities of the S &amp;amp; P 500 index. If last summer the company&amp;rsquo;s capitalization reached $1 trillion, then in November 2022 it was about $240 billion. Back in October 2021, Meta co-founder Mark Zuckerberg was the third-richest person in the world, and now he has moved to 29th place.</description></item></channel></rss>