<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Elizaveta Anokhina on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/elizaveta-anokhina/</link><description>Recent content in Elizaveta Anokhina on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 01:16:08 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/elizaveta-anokhina/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lobbyists, Obama Enemies, Corporate Dictators: The Story of the Koch Brothers</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62bc609c9a794728b8715e77/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 01:16:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62bc609c9a794728b8715e77/</guid><description>“A huge company you&amp;rsquo;ve never heard of” is often used to characterize Koch Industries, a diversified conglomerate originally engaged in oil refining. It is now the second largest private company in the US after Cargill. The company owes its success to the sons of the founder, Charles and David Koch: under their leadership, Koch Industries has gone from a company with annual sales of $250 million to a corporate giant with revenues of $115 billion (data for 2020).</description></item><item><title>Extroverts and lazy people with high salaries: how Twitter lived before Musk</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63774a499a7947963c0c3f14/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:26:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63774a499a7947963c0c3f14/</guid><description>In early November, a photo of a woman in a sleeping bag and a sleep mask on the floor of an office building went viral on Twitter. “When you need something from your Twitter boss Elon,” Twitter product manager Evan Jones captioned the picture. Twitter director of product management Esther Crawford, who was the lead, commented: &amp;ldquo;When your team is working around the clock to meet a deadline, you sleep at work.</description></item><item><title>Fashion designer Ralph Lauren: “I prepared for greatness from an early age”</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e3be69a79470810a89a6c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 15:38:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e3be69a79470810a89a6c/</guid><description>About a dreamer from the Bronx A student of one of the New York schools, Ralph Lifshitz, wrote in his graduation album in 1957 that he was going to become a millionaire, although at that time he did not even think how he would achieve this. Today, the whole world knows him as Ralph Lauren, and he clearly over fulfilled his plan: his fortune is estimated at $6.5 billion. Lauren&amp;rsquo;s business empire includes several lines of clothing, shoes and accessories, a brand of furniture and home goods, as well as several restaurants.</description></item><item><title>Sober billionaires: Buffett, Rybakov, Durov - about giving up alcohol</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635a6cbd9a7947127de2ddcc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 14:34:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635a6cbd9a7947127de2ddcc/</guid><description>Igor Rybakov “When I came to university, alcohol was disgusting to me. More precisely, I was neutral to him. But what happened among the students at the university? Well, there, let&amp;rsquo;s try beer there, and so on &amp;hellip; And then what happened? Well, I began to apply a little beer, then more, more, ” recalled the co-founder of TechnoNIKOL. Now Rybakov is convinced that alcohol, like drugs, is a way to distract from difficulties and drown out stress, which only delays the solution of problems and thereby exacerbates them.</description></item></channel></rss>