<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>articles on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/tags/articles/</link><description>Recent content in articles on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:30:45 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/tags/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why squiggles and sticking out tongue help you focus</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63622aa49a7947a9e99aa406/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:30:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63622aa49a7947a9e99aa406/</guid><description>An excerpt from Jen Martin&amp;rsquo;s book It&amp;rsquo;s Just Me. How science explains our oddities and habits, Alpina Publisher.
Why do I stick out my tongue to focus? The next time you see a baby who is doing something intently with his hands, follow him. Most likely, his tongue will stick out. Is it just a cute baby trait or something more?
Think about how you yourself do things that require precise movements, such as threading a needle or getting ready to send a billiard ball into a pocket.</description></item><item><title>Tea and Paper Newspaper: How Google CEO Sundar Pichai Starts the Day</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636234309a7947ae4b67e1b7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 02:38:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636234309a7947ae4b67e1b7/</guid><description>An Indian-born metallurgical engineer and cricket enthusiast, Sundar Pichai has led Google since 2015. In December 2019, he was appointed head of parent company Alphabet, which under his leadership became the fourth major technology corporation with a market value of more than $1 trillion.
The position requires Pichai to be able to multitask. Nevertheless, despite the high load, it works calmly, measuredly and without fuss. In this he is helped by morning rituals, with which he begins every day.</description></item><item><title>“I’m very busy”: how feeling constantly busy destroys life</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6363a7719a79472ee06e59b7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 02:49:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6363a7719a79472ee06e59b7/</guid><description>The day of a modern person is full of different tasks to the eyeballs. Trips to the office, work, gym, walking the dog, cooking, cleaning, visiting the doctor. It seems that you will never be able to cross off all the tasks from the to-do list. “I wish there were more hours in the day!” - this is the phrase that many people often end the day with.
Scientists call this state of haste time poverty.</description></item></channel></rss>