<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crypto on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/crypto/</link><description>Recent content in Crypto on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 01:56:21 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/topic/crypto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From $26.5 billion to $1: how Sam Bankman-Fried conquered the crypto world and lost everything</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6376576c9a7947568646d4b9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 01:56:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6376576c9a7947568646d4b9/</guid><description>The billionaire, the “golden boy” of the crypto industry, the owner of the successful FTX exchange - all this until recently referred to Sam Bankman-Fried, famous enough to get by with the initials SBF.
But in November, his position changed dramatically : he left the post of CEO of FTX and began bankruptcy proceedings (along with Alameda Research and 130 other partner companies), and his fortune was destroyed after the fall in the value of FTX&amp;rsquo;s business to $1.</description></item><item><title>“This is very, very bad for the crypto industry.” Who will be dragged to the bottom by the collapse of FTX</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264d99a79478caba1a753/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:34:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264d99a79478caba1a753/</guid><description>The echoes of the powerful collapse of FTX are still being felt in the crypto industry. On Monday, the value of digital currencies fell again as the market situation worsened over the weekend.
Some in the industry have said that the fall of FTX was &amp;ldquo;Lehman&amp;rsquo;s moment&amp;rdquo;, drawing parallels to the collapse of the investment bank in 2008, which was the starting point of the global crisis. The founder of Binance agreed with this metaphor, saying that comparing the current turmoil in the cryptocurrency market with the 2008 global financial crisis is an exact analogy.</description></item><item><title>Unreliable person: how the head of FTX lost $16 billion in a matter of days</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264559a79478c20090632/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 17:29:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264559a79478c20090632/</guid><description>FTX, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest centralized cryptocurrency exchanges, was valued at $32 billion in early 2022. The company was backed by well-known investors including US giants BlackRock and Tiger Global, Japanese investment bank SoftBank, and Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest pension fund, Ontario Teachers&amp;rsquo; Pension Plan.
At its peak, FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried was worth an estimated $26 billion. He earned a reputation as a “crypto savior” in the digital asset market. In the summer of 2022, after the collapse of the cryptocurrency market, Bankman-Fried actively supported crypto companies that found themselves in a difficult financial situation.</description></item></channel></rss>