<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kira Galkina on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/kira-galkina/</link><description>Recent content in Kira Galkina on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:14:24 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/kira-galkina/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There are strikes in the EU over wages. How will this affect corporate profits?</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6375071a9a79476e9270960a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:14:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6375071a9a79476e9270960a/</guid><description>In 2022, Europe&amp;rsquo;s largest companies are facing record inflation and the worst energy crisis in 40 years. Now corporations are preparing for new challenges.
Against the backdrop of inflation, the purchasing power of the population is falling, and workers are demanding higher salaries. Despite the fact that many European companies are experiencing a shortage of qualified personnel, not all firms are ready to accommodate employees, fearing that this will negatively affect the financial performance of the companies themselves.</description></item><item><title>Unreliable person: how the head of FTX lost $16 billion in a matter of days</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264559a79478c20090632/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 17:29:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/637264559a79478c20090632/</guid><description>FTX, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest centralized cryptocurrency exchanges, was valued at $32 billion in early 2022. The company was backed by well-known investors including US giants BlackRock and Tiger Global, Japanese investment bank SoftBank, and Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest pension fund, Ontario Teachers&amp;rsquo; Pension Plan.
At its peak, FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried was worth an estimated $26 billion. He earned a reputation as a “crypto savior” in the digital asset market. In the summer of 2022, after the collapse of the cryptocurrency market, Bankman-Fried actively supported crypto companies that found themselves in a difficult financial situation.</description></item></channel></rss>