<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Olga Kiseleva on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/olga-kiseleva/</link><description>Recent content in Olga Kiseleva on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 09:29:31 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/olga-kiseleva/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>“Pilates changed my life”: the head of the Kardashian-Jenner clan is about sports</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635105319a7947638b0f03c3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 09:29:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635105319a7947638b0f03c3/</guid><description>About sports and nutrition Successful entrepreneur, producer and media personality Kris Jenner (in her first marriage - Kardashian) raised six children. Now she is responsible for managing 15 different brands of her daughters: for example, Kim Kardashian launched Skims, a $3.2 billion lingerie and clothing brand in 2019, and Kylie Jenner created her own cosmetics line, Kylie Cosmetics, in which she had a stake a few years ago. Bought by Coty for $600 million.</description></item><item><title>“Bezos and Mandela inspire me”: McDonald's CEO on mentors</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ea2339a79472d7cc82744/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 09:25:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/634ea2339a79472d7cc82744/</guid><description>About a difficult start Chris Kempchinski took over McDonald&amp;rsquo;s at a difficult time. Former CEO Steve Easterbrook stepped down from his job due to an affair with female employees. Less than five months after Kempchinski&amp;rsquo;s appointment, the COVID-19 pandemic began, with McDonald&amp;rsquo;s having to temporarily close more than 36,000 restaurants around the world, causing revenue to plummet.
The head of McDonald&amp;rsquo;s is confident that during the crisis, you can focus on the short term.</description></item><item><title>IBM CEO Arvind Krishna: “Success is determined by curiosity and the ability to learn”</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635aa01a9a79472978af37f7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 09:22:12 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/635aa01a9a79472978af37f7/</guid><description>Arvind Krishna has always been attracted to engineering sciences, which combine mathematics and physics and at the same time find application in practice. He joined IBM in 1990 as a developer, and 30 years later, just a few months before the COVID-19 pandemic, he became the company&amp;rsquo;s CEO. Krishna faced an ambitious task - after a period of stagnation, to return a company with more than a century of history to the growth of financial indicators.</description></item><item><title>“I won my mother in the lottery”: Musk, Gates and Bezos - about their childhood experiences</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62b1b68a9a7947ba2729b9c1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 01:22:58 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62b1b68a9a7947ba2729b9c1/</guid><description>Bill Gates Microsoft founder Bill Gates was born into a wealthy family. His great-grandfather was the mayor of Seattle and a senator, his grandfather was a vice president of the National Bank. Parents, William and Mary Gates, held high positions in large companies. “My parents always encouraged me to do something I wasn’t good at, like different sports like swimming, football or hockey. As a child, it seemed rather pointless to me, but in the end it helped to develop leadership qualities in me, ”he said.</description></item><item><title>“Running helps to deal with problems”: the head of Lululemon is about sports</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63775e059a7947a05edaf4fd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 01:34:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63775e059a7947a05edaf4fd/</guid><description>Canadian company Lululemon Athletica, founded in 1998, has grown from a small firm specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s yoga pants to a sports retailer with 574 stores worldwide and a capitalization of $45.2 billion in just over 20 years. In 2020, the company ranked 25th in BrandZ&amp;rsquo;s Most Valuable Retail Brands. And in many respects this happened thanks to its current CEO Calvin McDonald.
He joined the company in 2018 and took over as CEO in 2021.</description></item><item><title>How to raise children correctly: Musk, Bezos, Gates, Branson answer</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62c816859a794734a1a1d2ab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 12:05:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62c816859a794734a1a1d2ab/</guid><description>Elon Musk Tesla founder Elon Musk has seven children: triplets Damian, Saxon and Kai and twins Griffin and Xavier from his first marriage. In 2020, the head of SpaceX Elon Musk and singer Grimes had a son, who was given the unusual name Ex Ash A-Twelv (X Æ A-12), and in 2022, a daughter, Exa Dark Syderil (abbreviated her name sounds Y). Musk&amp;rsquo;s first child from his marriage to his first wife, Justine Wilson, son Nevada, died at the age of ten weeks from sudden infant death syndrome.</description></item><item><title>Employees flee from energy giant ExxonMobil. What's Happening - Bloomberg</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636d239c9a7947b439cfe59d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 17:49:41 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636d239c9a7947b439cfe59d/</guid><description>ExxonMobil, an oil and gas company with a century and a half history, not only survived corporate upheavals and global crises, but also strengthened its position. Thanks to rising oil prices, Exxon shares have risen in price by 72% over the year, to $112 a share. This is an absolute historical maximum. The capitalization of the company is $456 billion, which makes it the largest oil and gas company in America and one of the leaders in the oil sector in the world.</description></item><item><title>Jira and Trello creator: "Successful people often feel like cheaters"</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e39369a7947074ed504a4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 01:38:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e39369a7947074ed504a4/</guid><description>About time management Mike Cannon-Brookes founded software company Atlassian with fellow student Scott Farquhar in 2002, right after graduating from university. Over 20 years, Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s capitalization has grown to $36 billion, and Cannon-Brooks&amp;rsquo; fortune to $9.4 billion. But despite the huge workload and responsibility, the entrepreneur always finds time for personal affairs.
He adheres to a strict daily routine and takes scheduling very seriously because &amp;ldquo;time cannot be turned back.&amp;rdquo; “I always try to find work-life balance,” he says.</description></item><item><title>“It’s all about concentration”: Robert Downey Jr. on Wing Chun</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636a3c039a794747e4e95bcf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:27:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636a3c039a794747e4e95bcf/</guid><description>During his career, 57-year-old American actor Robert Downey Jr. has starred in more than 70 films. He has won two Golden Globe Awards in 2001 and 2010. He also received several Oscar nominations. Downey Jr. has been on the Forbes list of Hollywood&amp;rsquo;s highest-paid actors four times, while topping the list three times.
But in the life of Downey Jr. there was a black streak. In 1992, at the age of 27, Downey played Charlie Chaplin in the film Chaplin and was named one of the most talented actors of the 1990s.</description></item><item><title>Tea and Paper Newspaper: How Google CEO Sundar Pichai Starts the Day</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636234309a7947ae4b67e1b7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 02:38:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636234309a7947ae4b67e1b7/</guid><description>An Indian-born metallurgical engineer and cricket enthusiast, Sundar Pichai has led Google since 2015. In December 2019, he was appointed head of parent company Alphabet, which under his leadership became the fourth major technology corporation with a market value of more than $1 trillion.
The position requires Pichai to be able to multitask. Nevertheless, despite the high load, it works calmly, measuredly and without fuss. In this he is helped by morning rituals, with which he begins every day.</description></item><item><title>“What have you learned in the last six months?”: the head of Accenture - to applicants</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6345798f9a79472589b493ce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 09:33:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6345798f9a79472589b493ce/</guid><description>About dangerous complacency Julie Sweet spent ten years at the large law firm Cravath, Swaine &amp;amp; Moore and rose to the position of partner when a recruiter friend called her and offered her a “great opportunity” to move to the consulting company Accenture. “I often think: why did I answer the phone then? Why did you agree to the meeting? I had two small children. I have been very successful. The future was set,” she recalls.</description></item><item><title>“An investment that pays off” - Marc Benioff on training and meditation</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6336f60e9a7947f3e37f9044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 09:54:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/6336f60e9a7947f3e37f9044/</guid><description>Salesforce co-founder and CEO Marc Benioff has been ranked as the Greatest Executive by multiple publications including Harvard Business Review and Fortune. He runs a $150 billion market cap company with over 73,000 employees.
When an entrepreneur is asked what helps him cope with stress at work, he answers briefly: “Mindfulness.” “I do mindfulness practice. I sit quietly in silence and try to let go of the stress that builds up during the week while I&amp;rsquo;m doing business,” he says.</description></item><item><title>“I want to die on the beach, not in the office”: Jack Ma on vacation</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62d50a1e9a7947e26d3eb585/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 10:43:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62d50a1e9a7947e26d3eb585/</guid><description>Jack Ma grew up in a poor family and was once a school English teacher. In 1999, he created the Alibaba marketplace: for 20 years under the leadership of Ma, the company entered the list of the most valuable companies in the world (ranks 33rd in the Forbes ranking), and the entrepreneur’s fortune grew to $24.5 billion. The founder of Alibaba believes that he has achieved this thanks to hard work.</description></item><item><title>“I wake up while the world is sleeping”: why the ex-head of Disney gets up before dawn</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62cbf7e69a79473062dcbeaf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 09:58:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62cbf7e69a79473062dcbeaf/</guid><description>Bob Iger was CEO of Disney from 2005 to 2020. During this time, the company has grown into a world leader in the entertainment industry. In 2019, Time magazine named the entrepreneur CEO of the year. As Iger wrote in his autobiography, he has a number of qualities and habits that helped him achieve success in his career. “For example, for as long as I can remember, I always woke up early and enjoyed this watch that belonged to me alone, while the rest of the world was sleeping,” says Eiger.</description></item><item><title>“The current me would be disgusted with myself at 20”: how Bill Gates rests</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62bd64c39a7947746a081795/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 10:09:58 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62bd64c39a7947746a081795/</guid><description>About sleep and weekends Microsoft co-founder Bill Gates is known for his hard work. He started the company when he was 20 years old. The billionaire assures that in those years he devoted the maximum amount of time to his business. “I didn’t have a single day off from 20 to 30 years old,” the 66-year-old entrepreneur said more than once in various interviews. Not a single day. On working days, especially at the very beginning, when the company was just getting on its feet, he was in the office until the evening, took a short break, and then returned to work for a few more hours.</description></item><item><title>“I’m like a ninja in a street fight”: Ray Dalio - on the impact of meditation</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62a342ee9a7947044aa75c86/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 10:13:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62a342ee9a7947044aa75c86/</guid><description>Meditation is the path to success An important place in the life of the American billionaire and founder of the investment company Bridgewater Associates, Ray Dalio, is occupied by transcendental meditation: the technique consists in repeating a mantra with closed eyes in a comfortable position for 15–20 minutes. It allows the entrepreneur to maintain clarity of mind and composure in any circumstances. “I owe a lot of my success in life to meditation, which helps me calm down, stay open to new things, think more clearly and outside the box,” says Dalio.</description></item></channel></rss>