<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Olga Kiseleva on Allwellbeing</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/olga-kiseleva/</link><description>Recent content in Olga Kiseleva on Allwellbeing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 01:22:58 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allwellbeing.github.io/author/olga-kiseleva/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>“I won my mother in the lottery”: Musk, Gates and Bezos - about their childhood experiences</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62b1b68a9a7947ba2729b9c1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 01:22:58 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62b1b68a9a7947ba2729b9c1/</guid><description>Bill Gates Microsoft founder Bill Gates was born into a wealthy family. His great-grandfather was the mayor of Seattle and a senator, his grandfather was a vice president of the National Bank. Parents, William and Mary Gates, held high positions in large companies. “My parents always encouraged me to do something I wasn’t good at, like different sports like swimming, football or hockey. As a child, it seemed rather pointless to me, but in the end it helped to develop leadership qualities in me, ”he said.</description></item><item><title>“Running helps to deal with problems”: the head of Lululemon is about sports</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63775e059a7947a05edaf4fd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 01:34:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/63775e059a7947a05edaf4fd/</guid><description>Canadian company Lululemon Athletica, founded in 1998, has grown from a small firm specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s yoga pants to a sports retailer with 574 stores worldwide and a capitalization of $45.2 billion in just over 20 years. In 2020, the company ranked 25th in BrandZ&amp;rsquo;s Most Valuable Retail Brands. And in many respects this happened thanks to its current CEO Calvin McDonald.
He joined the company in 2018 and took over as CEO in 2021.</description></item><item><title>How to raise children correctly: Musk, Bezos, Gates, Branson answer</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62c816859a794734a1a1d2ab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 12:05:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/62c816859a794734a1a1d2ab/</guid><description>Elon Musk Tesla founder Elon Musk has seven children: triplets Damian, Saxon and Kai and twins Griffin and Xavier from his first marriage. In 2020, the head of SpaceX Elon Musk and singer Grimes had a son, who was given the unusual name Ex Ash A-Twelv (X Æ A-12), and in 2022, a daughter, Exa Dark Syderil (abbreviated her name sounds Y). Musk&amp;rsquo;s first child from his marriage to his first wife, Justine Wilson, son Nevada, died at the age of ten weeks from sudden infant death syndrome.</description></item><item><title>Employees flee from energy giant ExxonMobil. What's Happening - Bloomberg</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636d239c9a7947b439cfe59d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 17:49:41 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636d239c9a7947b439cfe59d/</guid><description>ExxonMobil, an oil and gas company with a century and a half history, not only survived corporate upheavals and global crises, but also strengthened its position. Thanks to rising oil prices, Exxon shares have risen in price by 72% over the year, to $112 a share. This is an absolute historical maximum. The capitalization of the company is $456 billion, which makes it the largest oil and gas company in America and one of the leaders in the oil sector in the world.</description></item><item><title>Jira and Trello creator: "Successful people often feel like cheaters"</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e39369a7947074ed504a4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 01:38:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636e39369a7947074ed504a4/</guid><description>About time management Mike Cannon-Brookes founded software company Atlassian with fellow student Scott Farquhar in 2002, right after graduating from university. Over 20 years, Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s capitalization has grown to $36 billion, and Cannon-Brooks&amp;rsquo; fortune to $9.4 billion. But despite the huge workload and responsibility, the entrepreneur always finds time for personal affairs.
He adheres to a strict daily routine and takes scheduling very seriously because &amp;ldquo;time cannot be turned back.&amp;rdquo; “I always try to find work-life balance,” he says.</description></item><item><title>“It’s all about concentration”: Robert Downey Jr. on Wing Chun</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636a3c039a794747e4e95bcf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:27:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636a3c039a794747e4e95bcf/</guid><description>During his career, 57-year-old American actor Robert Downey Jr. has starred in more than 70 films. He has won two Golden Globe Awards in 2001 and 2010. He also received several Oscar nominations. Downey Jr. has been on the Forbes list of Hollywood&amp;rsquo;s highest-paid actors four times, while topping the list three times.
But in the life of Downey Jr. there was a black streak. In 1992, at the age of 27, Downey played Charlie Chaplin in the film Chaplin and was named one of the most talented actors of the 1990s.</description></item><item><title>Tea and Paper Newspaper: How Google CEO Sundar Pichai Starts the Day</title><link>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636234309a7947ae4b67e1b7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 02:38:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://allwellbeing.github.io/news/636234309a7947ae4b67e1b7/</guid><description>An Indian-born metallurgical engineer and cricket enthusiast, Sundar Pichai has led Google since 2015. In December 2019, he was appointed head of parent company Alphabet, which under his leadership became the fourth major technology corporation with a market value of more than $1 trillion.
The position requires Pichai to be able to multitask. Nevertheless, despite the high load, it works calmly, measuredly and without fuss. In this he is helped by morning rituals, with which he begins every day.</description></item></channel></rss>